<?xml version="1.0"?>
<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="en-US">

<!-- Opening Hook -->
<prosody rate="slow" pitch="-2st">
What would you do<break time="800ms"/> if you found a human skeleton<break time="1s"/> hanging by strings<break time="800ms"/> of human hair?
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="medium" volume="loud">
In nineteen eighty-two,<break time="600ms"/> deep inside an abandoned West Virginia coal mine,<break time="1s"/> they found <emphasis level="strong">forty-four</emphasis> of them.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" pitch="-1st">
Each one<break time="500ms"/> posed<break time="500ms"/> like a marionette.<break time="1s"/> Each one<break time="500ms"/> handcrafted<break time="800ms"/> by someone<break time="600ms"/> who refused<break time="500ms"/> to be alone.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="medium">
Today,<break time="500ms"/> we're uncovering the forgotten case<break time="600ms"/> that West Virginia tried to erase<break time="1s"/> a story of grief,<break time="500ms"/> madness,<break time="800ms"/> and the silence of the mountains<break time="600ms"/> that still echo<break time="500ms"/> with her name.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="medium-slow">
Comment down below<break time="400ms"/> from where you're watching<break time="800ms"/> because this story isn't just about the past.<break time="1s"/> It's about how isolation<break time="600ms"/> still changes people<break time="1s"/> even today.
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<!-- Chapter 1: The Setting -->
<prosody rate="slow" pitch="-2st" volume="medium">
It was eighteen eighty-seven,<break time="1s"/> and the coal mines of Widow's Hollow<break time="800ms"/> were running dry.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="medium-slow">
What had once been a thriving mining community<break time="500ms"/> of three hundred souls<break time="800ms"/> had dwindled to barely fifty desperate people<break time="600ms"/> clinging to hope<break time="1s"/> in a landscape of fog-shrouded peaks<break time="600ms"/> and treacherous hollows.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
The mountains rose<break time="500ms"/> like prison walls<break time="600ms"/> on either side of the settlement,<break time="800ms"/> their slopes so steep<break time="600ms"/> that sunlight only reached the valley floor<break time="500ms"/> for three hours each day,<break time="1s"/> casting the town in perpetual twilight<break time="800ms"/> that seemed to seep<break time="600ms"/> into the very souls<break time="500ms"/> of those who remained.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="medium" pitch="-1st">
The hollow itself<break time="600ms"/> was named for the dozens of women<break time="500ms"/> who had lost their husbands to the mines<break time="600ms"/> over the years.<break time="1s"/> Cave-ins,<break time="500ms"/> gas explosions,<break time="500ms"/> flooding,<break time="500ms"/> black lung<break time="1s"/> the mountain claimed men<break time="600ms"/> with ruthless efficiency,<break time="800ms"/> leaving behind widows<break time="600ms"/> who either fled to find new lives elsewhere<break time="800ms"/> or stayed<break time="600ms"/> to slowly waste away<break time="500ms"/> in the shadow of the peaks<break time="600ms"/> that had devoured their futures.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
The locals said the mountain was hungry,<break time="1s"/> that it fed on the hopes and dreams<break time="600ms"/> of those who dared to dig<break time="500ms"/> into its flesh.
</prosody>

<break time="2.5s"/>

<!-- Introducing Constance -->
<prosody rate="medium-slow" pitch="-1st">
In this dying place,<break time="800ms"/> there lived a woman<break time="600ms"/> who would become known<break time="500ms"/> only as<break time="800ms"/> <emphasis level="strong">The Bone Collector</emphasis>.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="medium">
Her real name was Constance Blackwood,<break time="600ms"/> a thirty-eight-year-old widow<break time="500ms"/> who had arrived in Widow's Hollow<break time="400ms"/> five years earlier<break time="600ms"/> with her husband,<break time="500ms"/> a mining engineer<break time="400ms"/> who had promised her a new life<break time="400ms"/> in the mountains.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
He was an educated man from Philadelphia,<break time="600ms"/> full of ideas about modern mining techniques<break time="500ms"/> and dreams of striking it rich<break time="600ms"/> in the untapped veins of Appalachian coal.<break time="1.5s"/> That promise<break time="800ms"/> died with him<break time="600ms"/> six months later<break time="800ms"/> when a tunnel collapse claimed his life<break time="600ms"/> along with seventeen other men,<break time="1s"/> their bodies so thoroughly crushed and buried<break time="600ms"/> that only three<break time="500ms"/> were ever recovered<break time="500ms"/> for proper burial.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
Constance should have left.<break time="1s"/> Most widows did,<break time="600ms"/> packing up their meager belongings<break time="500ms"/> and heading back to wherever they'd come from,<break time="800ms"/> or moving to larger cities<break time="500ms"/> where they might find work<break time="400ms"/> or remarry.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="medium-slow" pitch="-1st">
But she stayed<break time="1s"/> in the small timber house at the edge of town,<break time="600ms"/> the one that her husband had built<break time="400ms"/> with his own hands<break time="600ms"/> during their first months in Widow's Hollow.<break time="1s"/> The house backed directly onto the abandoned mine shafts<break time="600ms"/> that honeycombed the mountainside<break time="500ms"/> like the tunnels of some giant insect,<break time="1s"/> dark entrances<break time="600ms"/> that exhaled cold, damp air<break time="500ms"/> that smelled of earth<break time="800ms"/> and decay.
</prosody>

<break time="2.5s"/>

<!-- The Transformation Begins -->
<prosody rate="slow">
The townspeople rarely saw her after the funeral,<break time="800ms"/> and when they did,<break time="600ms"/> she moved through the muddy streets<break time="500ms"/> like a shadow,<break time="1s"/> her black mourning dress<break time="500ms"/> never replaced,<break time="800ms"/> her pale face always hidden<break time="500ms"/> beneath a wide-brimmed hat<break time="600ms"/> that cast her features<break time="500ms"/> in permanent darkness.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="medium-slow">
The few who spoke to her<break time="400ms"/> in those early days of her widowhood<break time="600ms"/> reported that she seemed to have aged<break time="400ms"/> decades<break time="500ms"/> in mere months.<break time="1s"/> Her eyes,<break time="600ms"/> once bright and full of the excitement<break time="400ms"/> of a city woman experiencing mountain life,<break time="800ms"/> had become hollow<break time="600ms"/> and distant,<break time="800ms"/> as if she were looking at something<break time="500ms"/> far beyond the visible world.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<!-- The Reverend's Discovery -->
<prosody rate="medium">
The local pastor,<break time="400ms"/> Reverend Josiah Blackburn,<break time="600ms"/> tried to minister to her<break time="400ms"/> in those first months.<break time="1s"/> He would climb the steep path to her house<break time="500ms"/> every Sunday after services,<break time="600ms"/> carrying food donated by the congregation<break time="500ms"/> and offering what comfort he could<break time="400ms"/> to a woman clearly drowning in grief.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
But his visits<break time="600ms"/> became increasingly uncomfortable.<break time="1s"/> Constance would sit in silence,<break time="600ms"/> staring at him with those empty eyes,<break time="800ms"/> barely touching the food he brought.<break time="1s"/> Her house,<break time="500ms"/> once neat and well-kept,<break time="600ms"/> began to deteriorate.<break time="1s"/> Dust gathered on surfaces.<break time="800ms"/> Dishes piled up unwashed.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft" pitch="-1st">
And there was a smell<break time="1s"/> subtle at first,<break time="600ms"/> but growing stronger with each visit<break time="1s"/> that reminded Reverend Blackburn<break time="600ms"/> of the funeral parlor<break time="500ms"/> where he'd blessed so many bodies<break time="500ms"/> before burial.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="medium-slow">
On his final visit,<break time="800ms"/> three months after her husband's death,<break time="600ms"/> the reverend found Constance<break time="500ms"/> in the back room of her house,<break time="800ms"/> a space that had once been her husband's study.<break time="1s"/> She had converted it<break time="600ms"/> into some kind of workshop.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
There were books on anatomy<break time="500ms"/> spread across the desk<break time="800ms"/> medical texts<break time="600ms"/> that must have belonged to her husband's collection.<break time="1s"/> There were drawings on the walls,<break time="600ms"/> detailed sketches of human skeletons<break time="500ms"/> in various poses.<break time="1.5s"/> And on the table,<break time="800ms"/> partially covered by a cloth,<break time="800ms"/> was something<break time="600ms"/> that made Reverend Blackburn's stomach<break time="500ms"/> turn.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="medium" pitch="-2st">
It was a human skull,<break time="1s"/> cleaned and bleached white,<break time="800ms"/> sitting on a wooden stand<break time="600ms"/> that Constance had apparently carved<break time="500ms"/> herself.
</prosody>

<break time="2.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
When the reverend asked her about it,<break time="800ms"/> her response<break time="600ms"/> chilled him<break time="500ms"/> to the bone.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" pitch="-1st" volume="soft">
"It's beautiful,<break time="500ms"/> isn't it?"<break time="1s"/> she said,<break time="600ms"/> her voice dreamy and distant.<break time="1.5s"/> "This is all that remains of us<break time="500ms"/> in the end.<break time="1s"/> Everything else<break time="800ms"/> the flesh,<break time="500ms"/> the hopes,<break time="500ms"/> the dreams,<break time="500ms"/> the love<break time="1s"/> it all rots away.<break time="1.5s"/> But the bones remain.<break time="1s"/> The bones<break time="800ms"/> are eternal."
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<!-- The Disappearances Begin -->
<prosody rate="medium-slow" pitch="-1st">
Reverend Blackburn left that day<break time="600ms"/> and never returned.<break time="1s"/> He told no one what he'd seen,<break time="600ms"/> convincing himself that grief took many forms<break time="500ms"/> and that Constance would eventually emerge<break time="500ms"/> from her darkness.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="medium">
He couldn't have been<break time="800ms"/> more wrong.
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<prosody rate="medium">
What made Constance different from other reclusive widows<break time="600ms"/> wasn't her grief.<break time="1s"/> It was what she did<break time="500ms"/> with that grief.<break time="1s"/> What she created<break time="500ms"/> in the darkness of those abandoned mines.<break time="1s"/> What she built<break time="600ms"/> in a workshop<break time="500ms"/> that no living person<break time="500ms"/> was meant to discover.
</prosody>

<break time="2.5s"/>

<prosody rate="medium-slow">
The first disappearance happened<break time="500ms"/> in March of eighteen eighty-seven,<break time="800ms"/> six months after Constance's last conversation<break time="400ms"/> with Reverend Blackburn.<break time="1s"/> A prospector named William Tate<break time="500ms"/> vanished while exploring the old mine shafts,<break time="600ms"/> searching for veins of coal<break time="400ms"/> that the mining company might have missed.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
Tate was a familiar figure in Widow's Hollow<break time="800ms"/> a grizzled old-timer<break time="500ms"/> who'd been prospecting in Appalachia<break time="400ms"/> for thirty years.<break time="1s"/> He knew the mountains better than most,<break time="600ms"/> understood the dangers of unstable tunnels<break time="500ms"/> and poisonous gases<break time="500ms"/> that could kill a man<break time="500ms"/> in seconds.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="medium">
His mule was found wandering the main street<break time="500ms"/> three days later,<break time="800ms"/> still saddled<break time="600ms"/> but without its rider.<break time="1s"/> Tate's supplies were still strapped to the animal<break time="600ms"/> food,<break time="400ms"/> water,<break time="400ms"/> mining equipment<break time="800ms"/> everything<break time="600ms"/> except the man himself.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
In a place like Widow's Hollow,<break time="600ms"/> where men routinely fell down shafts<break time="500ms"/> or got lost in the labyrinth of tunnels,<break time="800ms"/> one missing prospector<break time="600ms"/> barely warranted investigation.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<!-- Sarah Mitchell -->
<prosody rate="medium-slow" pitch="-1st">
The second disappearance<break time="800ms"/> was more troubling.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="medium">
Sarah Mitchell,<break time="600ms"/> a young woman of nineteen,<break time="600ms"/> disappeared while collecting water<break time="400ms"/> from the mountain creek<break time="400ms"/> that fed the town's water supply.<break time="1s"/> It was a bright April morning,<break time="600ms"/> and several people saw her walking toward the creek<break time="500ms"/> with her bucket.<break time="1.5s"/> She never returned.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
Her bucket was found at the water's edge,<break time="800ms"/> still full,<break time="800ms"/> with no signs of a struggle.<break time="1s"/> The water sat undisturbed,<break time="600ms"/> reflecting the pale morning sky<break time="600ms"/> like a mirror.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="medium-slow">
Sarah was well-liked in the community,<break time="600ms"/> the daughter of one of the few remaining mining supervisors.<break time="800ms"/> She was engaged to be married<break time="500ms"/> to James Cooper,<break time="600ms"/> a mine foreman<break time="400ms"/> who had managed to save enough money<break time="500ms"/> to eventually leave Widow's Hollow<break time="500ms"/> and start a new life with his bride<break time="400ms"/> in a larger town.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
Sarah had been making wedding plans,<break time="600ms"/> talking excitedly about the dress she was sewing,<break time="600ms"/> the small house they would rent,<break time="600ms"/> the children they would have<break time="500ms"/> far away from the cursed mountains.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="medium">
Her fiancé,<break time="400ms"/> James Cooper,<break time="600ms"/> was devastated.<break time="1s"/> He organized search parties<break time="500ms"/> that combed the hollow for weeks,<break time="600ms"/> climbing treacherous slopes<break time="500ms"/> and wading through fog<break time="500ms"/> so thick<break time="400ms"/> you couldn't see your hand<break time="400ms"/> in front of your face.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
Men searched every abandoned mine entrance,<break time="600ms"/> every cave,<break time="500ms"/> every ravine<break time="500ms"/> where a body might have fallen.<break time="1s"/> They called her name<break time="500ms"/> until their voices were hoarse,<break time="800ms"/> the sound echoing off the mountain walls<break time="600ms"/> and returning to them<break time="500ms"/> like mocking ghosts.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
They found nothing.<break time="1.5s"/> Sarah Mitchell had simply vanished,<break time="800ms"/> as if the mountain had opened up<break time="600ms"/> and swallowed her<break time="500ms"/> whole.
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<!-- More Disappearances -->
<prosody rate="medium-slow" pitch="-1st">
By summer,<break time="800ms"/> five more people had vanished.<break time="1.5s"/> The pattern<break time="600ms"/> was impossible to ignore.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="medium">
All disappeared near the old mine entrances.<break time="800ms"/> All vanished without a trace.<break time="1s"/> And all were last seen<break time="500ms"/> in the vicinity of Constance Blackwood's timber house,<break time="800ms"/> perched like a crow's nest<break time="500ms"/> on the ridge above the hollow.
</prosody>

<break time="2.5s"/>

<!-- Marshal Price Investigation -->
<prosody rate="medium-slow">
The local marshal,<break time="400ms"/> Dalton Price,<break time="600ms"/> was a weathered man in his late fifties<break time="500ms"/> who had spent twenty years enforcing law<break time="400ms"/> in the Appalachian mountains<break time="600ms"/> where justice was often delivered at gunpoint<break time="500ms"/> rather than in courtrooms.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
He'd seen every kind of crime<break time="500ms"/> that desperate poverty and isolation could produce<break time="800ms"/> moonshine wars that left entire families dead,<break time="600ms"/> claim-jumping disputes settled with dynamite,<break time="600ms"/> domestic violence that ended in murder.<break time="1.5s"/> But a serial disappearance pattern like this<break time="800ms"/> was unprecedented<break time="500ms"/> in his experience.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="medium">
Price was a practical soul,<break time="600ms"/> not given to superstition or wild theories.<break time="1s"/> He knew that accusing a widow without evidence<break time="500ms"/> was dangerous,<break time="600ms"/> particularly in a community<break time="400ms"/> already fraying at the edges.<break time="1s"/> Mountain folk had their own codes of justice,<break time="600ms"/> and a widow<break time="800ms"/> especially one who'd lost her husband to the mines<break time="800ms"/> occupied a protected status<break time="400ms"/> in the social hierarchy.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
But he also knew<break time="600ms"/> that seven disappearances in six months<break time="800ms"/> was more than coincidence.<break time="1s"/> The statistical probability alone<break time="600ms"/> suggested something sinister<break time="500ms"/> at work.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="medium-slow">
He began to watch Constance Blackwood's house<break time="500ms"/> from a distance,<break time="800ms"/> spending hours hidden in the tree line,<break time="600ms"/> observing her movements.<break time="1s"/> What he saw<break time="800ms"/> troubled him.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
She kept strange hours,<break time="600ms"/> often disappearing into the mine entrances<break time="500ms"/> near her property at night,<break time="800ms"/> carrying lanterns and canvas bags<break time="500ms"/> whose contents he couldn't identify.<break time="1s"/> Sometimes she would emerge hours later,<break time="600ms"/> the bags apparently empty.<break time="1s"/> Other times she would return multiple times<break time="500ms"/> in a single night,<break time="800ms"/> as if transporting something<break time="600ms"/> piece<break time="500ms"/> by piece.
</prosody>

<break time="2.5s"/>

<!-- The Preacher's Accusation -->
<prosody rate="medium-slow" pitch="-1st">
It was a traveling preacher named Elijah Stone<break time="800ms"/> who first voiced the suspicions<break time="500ms"/> that everyone was thinking<break time="500ms"/> but no one dared say aloud.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="medium">
Stone was a firebrand evangelist<break time="500ms"/> who rode a circuit through the Appalachian mountains,<break time="600ms"/> bringing hellfire sermons<break time="400ms"/> to isolated communities<break time="400ms"/> that rarely saw ordained ministers.<break time="1s"/> He arrived in Widow's Hollow<break time="500ms"/> in late August,<break time="600ms"/> having heard about the disappearances<break time="500ms"/> from travelers on the road.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
During a tent revival on a humid August evening,<break time="800ms"/> with half the remaining townspeople<break time="500ms"/> gathered under canvas<break time="500ms"/> to pray for deliverance<break time="400ms"/> from whatever evil had infected their community,<break time="1s"/> Stone worked himself<break time="600ms"/> into a prophetic frenzy.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="loud" pitch="-1st">
"There walks among us,"<break time="1s"/> he thundered,<break time="600ms"/> pointing a trembling finger<break time="500ms"/> toward the dark outline of Constance's house on the ridge,<break time="1.5s"/> "a creature that wears the shape of woman<break time="800ms"/> but harbors the soul<break time="600ms"/> of something far more terrible!<break time="1.5s"/> She collects<break time="600ms"/> what God never meant to be collected!<break time="1s"/> She builds<break time="600ms"/> what should never be built!<break time="1.5s"/> And in the darkness beneath our feet,<break time="800ms"/> in those cursed mines<break time="500ms"/> that have already swallowed so many good men,<break time="1s"/> she creates monuments<break time="800ms"/> to her own damnation!"
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<!-- James Cooper's Descent -->
<prosody rate="medium-slow">
That someone<break time="600ms"/> turned out to be James Cooper,<break time="800ms"/> the fiancé of Sarah Mitchell.<break time="1.5s"/> Grief had transformed him<break time="600ms"/> from a careful, methodical mine foreman<break time="600ms"/> into a man<break time="500ms"/> with nothing left to lose.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
In the three months since Sarah's disappearance,<break time="800ms"/> he'd aged visibly.<break time="1s"/> His hair had gone gray at the temples.<break time="800ms"/> His face had become gaunt.<break time="1s"/> He'd lost weight,<break time="600ms"/> unable to eat,<break time="500ms"/> unable to sleep,<break time="800ms"/> haunted by dreams of Sarah<break time="600ms"/> calling out to him<break time="500ms"/> from somewhere in the darkness<break time="500ms"/> beneath the mountain.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="medium">
Cooper approached Marshal Price<break time="500ms"/> the day after the revival meeting.<break time="1s"/> "I'll go into the mines,"<break time="800ms"/> he said simply.<break time="1s"/> "I'll find out what happened to Sarah.<break time="800ms"/> And if that woman had anything to do with it,<break time="600ms"/> I'll find the proof."
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="medium-slow">
Cooper entered the mines<break time="500ms"/> on September third,<break time="400ms"/> eighteen eighty-seven,<break time="800ms"/> just as dawn was breaking<break time="500ms"/> over the mountain peaks.<break time="1s"/> The entrance he chose<break time="500ms"/> was partially hidden by overgrown brush,<break time="600ms"/> less than a hundred yards<break time="500ms"/> from Constance's house.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
He carried a lantern in one hand,<break time="600ms"/> a pistol in the other,<break time="800ms"/> and enough rope coiled around his shoulders<break time="500ms"/> to mark his trail<break time="400ms"/> back to the surface.<break time="1s"/> He told Marshal Price<break time="500ms"/> he would return before nightfall,<break time="800ms"/> that he would explore only the main tunnels<break time="500ms"/> and avoid any branches<break time="400ms"/> that looked unstable.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
When darkness fell<break time="800ms"/> and Cooper hadn't emerged,<break time="1s"/> Price assumed the worst<break time="800ms"/> that the mines had claimed another victim,<break time="800ms"/> that the mountain had swallowed him whole<break time="600ms"/> like it had swallowed so many others.
</prosody>

<break time="2.5s"/>

<!-- Cooper's Return -->
<prosody rate="medium-slow" pitch="-1st">
But Cooper did return.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="medium">
Three days later,<break time="600ms"/> at first light,<break time="800ms"/> he stumbled out of a mine entrance<break time="500ms"/> on the far side of the mountain,<break time="800ms"/> nearly two miles from where he'd entered.<break time="1s"/> He was covered in coal dust<break time="500ms"/> and something else,<break time="800ms"/> something white and powdery<break time="600ms"/> that Marshal Price would later identify<break time="500ms"/> as lime,<break time="800ms"/> the same chemical used to speed decomposition<break time="500ms"/> in graves.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
Cooper's clothes were torn,<break time="600ms"/> his hands were bleeding<break time="500ms"/> from climbing through narrow passages,<break time="800ms"/> and his face was haggard,<break time="800ms"/> bearing the expression of a man<break time="600ms"/> who'd seen something<break time="500ms"/> that fundamentally altered<break time="500ms"/> his understanding of human nature.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
His eyes held a horror<break time="800ms"/> that would never fully leave them,<break time="1s"/> a thousand-yard stare<break time="600ms"/> that Price had seen before<break time="500ms"/> only in soldiers<break time="500ms"/> who'd survived particularly brutal battles.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
Cooper couldn't speak<break time="800ms"/> for nearly an hour after his emergence.<break time="1s"/> He simply sat on a rock<break time="500ms"/> beside the mine entrance,<break time="800ms"/> trembling despite the warm September sun,<break time="800ms"/> occasionally dry-heaving<break time="600ms"/> though his stomach was long empty.
</prosody>

<break time="2.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" pitch="-2st">
When Cooper finally found his voice,<break time="1s"/> his testimony<break time="800ms"/> would change everything.
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<!-- The Workshop Discovery -->
<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
"There's a workshop,"<break time="1s"/> he whispered,<break time="800ms"/> his hands trembling so violently<break time="600ms"/> he had to clasp them together.<break time="1.5s"/> "Deep in the mine,<break time="600ms"/> where three tunnels meet<break time="500ms"/> in a natural chamber.<break time="1s"/> She's turned it into<break time="1s"/> into a studio.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
There are tables made from timber supports,<break time="600ms"/> tools hanging from the walls<break time="500ms"/> like a surgeon's instruments,<break time="800ms"/> chemicals in bottles<break time="500ms"/> lined up like a pharmacist's shop.<break time="1.5s"/> And the walls<break time="1.5s"/>
</prosody>

<break time="1s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
The walls are lined with them.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" pitch="-1st">
Forty-three human skeletons,<break time="1s"/> all perfectly cleaned<break time="600ms"/> and articulated.<break time="1.5s"/> But they're not just displayed<break time="500ms"/> like in some medical school.<break time="1s"/> They're<break time="1s"/> arranged.<break time="1s"/> Posed.<break time="1s"/> Like puppets in a theater<break time="600ms"/> or wax figures in a museum."
</prosody>

<break time="2.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
He paused,<break time="800ms"/> fighting to keep control of himself,<break time="800ms"/> his breath coming in short gasps.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
"Some are sitting in chairs<break time="500ms"/> she built from bone and timber.<break time="1s"/> Others are standing,<break time="600ms"/> held upright by wires<break time="500ms"/> made from human hair.<break time="1.5s"/> There's a dining table<break time="600ms"/> with six skeletons seated around it,<break time="800ms"/> set with plates<break time="500ms"/> made from skulls<break time="500ms"/> cut in half and polished.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" pitch="-1st">
There's a ballroom scene<break time="800ms"/> with dancing figures<break time="600ms"/> whose bones are connected<break time="500ms"/> by copper wire and sinew<break time="600ms"/> threaded through holes<break time="500ms"/> she drilled<break time="500ms"/> in the bones themselves."
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
Cooper's description continued,<break time="800ms"/> each detail<break time="600ms"/> more horrifying than the last.<break time="1.5s"/> He described a skeleton<break time="500ms"/> posed as if playing a violin<break time="500ms"/> made from a human ribcage.<break time="1.5s"/> Another arranged as if reading a book<break time="600ms"/> whose pages were actually human skin,<break time="800ms"/> tanned and preserved.<break time="1.5s"/> A small skeleton<break time="1s"/> a child<break time="1s"/> positioned as if sleeping<break time="600ms"/> in a cradle constructed<break time="500ms"/> from larger bones.
</prosody>

<break time="2.5s"/>

<prosody rate="medium-slow">
The level of detail,<break time="600ms"/> the obvious care and artistry<break time="500ms"/> that had gone into each display,<break time="800ms"/> made the horror<break time="800ms"/> even more profound.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
The workshop itself<break time="600ms"/> was a marvel of macabre craftsmanship.<break time="1s"/> Constance had spent years<break time="600ms"/> perfecting her techniques,<break time="800ms"/> learning anatomy<break time="500ms"/> through gruesome trial and error.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="medium-slow">
She had developed methods<break time="500ms"/> for cleaning bones using lye<break time="500ms"/> purchased from the general store<break time="400ms"/> under the guise of soap-making,<break time="800ms"/> for bleaching them white<break time="500ms"/> using chemicals she claimed<break time="400ms"/> were for preserving herbs,<break time="800ms"/> for articulating them into poses<break time="500ms"/> that mimicked life<break time="600ms"/> with unsettling accuracy.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
Cooper described vats of chemicals<break time="600ms"/> where bones soaked,<break time="800ms"/> slowly dissolving away<break time="500ms"/> the flesh and connective tissue.<break time="1s"/> There were drying racks<break time="600ms"/> where cleaned bones were laid out to cure.<break time="1s"/> There was a workbench<break time="500ms"/> covered in tools<break time="800ms"/> saws,<break time="400ms"/> drills,<break time="400ms"/> files,<break time="400ms"/> awls<break time="800ms"/> all meticulously maintained<break time="500ms"/> and organized.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
And there were diagrams on the walls,<break time="800ms"/> anatomical drawings<break time="600ms"/> showing how bones connected,<break time="600ms"/> how joints functioned,<break time="600ms"/> how to pose a skeleton<break time="500ms"/> to suggest movement<break time="600ms"/> and emotion.
</prosody>

<break time="2.5s"/>

<!-- The Journal -->
<prosody rate="medium-slow" pitch="-1st">
But the most disturbing aspect<break time="600ms"/> of Cooper's testimony<break time="800ms"/> was what he'd found<break time="600ms"/> in Constance's journal,<break time="1s"/> sitting open on her workbench<break time="600ms"/> beside a half-articulated skeleton<break time="600ms"/> that he recognized with horror<break time="800ms"/> as belonging to Timothy Wells,<break time="800ms"/> a fellow miner<break time="500ms"/> who'd disappeared<break time="500ms"/> just two weeks prior.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
The bones were still slightly yellow,<break time="800ms"/> not yet fully bleached,<break time="800ms"/> still smelling faintly<break time="600ms"/> of the chemicals used to clean them.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="medium">
The journal was a large leather-bound book,<break time="600ms"/> its pages covered<break time="400ms"/> in neat, elegant handwriting.<break time="1s"/> It contained detailed notes<break time="500ms"/> on each of her "subjects"<break time="1s"/> their names,<break time="500ms"/> the dates they were acquired,<break time="500ms"/> their physical characteristics,<break time="600ms"/> and extensive notes<break time="500ms"/> on how their skeletons would be used<break time="500ms"/> in her growing collection.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
She documented their heights,<break time="500ms"/> their builds,<break time="500ms"/> the condition of their teeth,<break time="500ms"/> the state of their bones.<break time="1s"/> She noted any abnormalities<break time="800ms"/> old fractures,<break time="500ms"/> arthritis,<break time="500ms"/> skeletal deformities<break time="800ms"/> and described how these features<break time="500ms"/> would enhance or limit their use<break time="500ms"/> in her displays.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
She wrote about her work<break time="600ms"/> with the pride of an artist<break time="500ms"/> discussing her masterpieces.<break time="1s"/> She described herself as a sculptor<break time="600ms"/> working in the medium of death itself,<break time="1s"/> creating tableaus that captured the essence<break time="600ms"/> of the life<break time="500ms"/> that Widow's Hollow had stolen from her.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
Each skeleton in her collection<break time="600ms"/> represented someone who,<break time="500ms"/> like her husband,<break time="600ms"/> had been consumed by the mines.<break time="1s"/> She was simply making that consumption<break time="600ms"/> visible,<break time="600ms"/> permanent,<break time="800ms"/> beautiful<break time="600ms"/> in its own terrible way.
</prosody>

<break time="2.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft" pitch="-1st">
"She doesn't see them as victims,"<break time="1s"/> Cooper said,<break time="600ms"/> his voice hollow,<break time="600ms"/> emotionless.<break time="1.5s"/> "She sees them as her art.<break time="1s"/> Her legacy.<break time="1s"/> Her way of making death<break time="600ms"/> mean something.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
She wrote that the mountains<break time="500ms"/> take and take and take,<break time="800ms"/> swallowing people whole<break time="600ms"/> and leaving nothing behind<break time="500ms"/> but grief and empty spaces.<break time="1.5s"/> She said she was preserving<break time="600ms"/> what the mountains would otherwise erase<break time="500ms"/> forever.<break time="1.5s"/> She actually believes<break time="800ms"/> she's doing something noble,<break time="800ms"/> something important."
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
Cooper described one passage from the journal<break time="600ms"/> that haunted him particularly,<break time="800ms"/> a passage he'd memorized<break time="600ms"/> during his three days trapped in the tunnels:
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" pitch="-2st" volume="soft">
"In the darkness beneath Appalachia,<break time="800ms"/> I have created my gallery of the lost.<break time="1.5s"/> Each bone tells a story<break time="600ms"/> that the mountains would silence.<break time="1.5s"/> I am not a monster.<break time="1s"/> I am a chronicler.<break time="1s"/> I am an artist.<break time="1.5s"/> I am the only one<break time="600ms"/> who remembers their names,<break time="500ms"/> their faces,<break time="500ms"/> the way they walked and talked<break time="500ms"/> and breathed.<break time="1.5s"/> In my gallery,<break time="800ms"/> they are eternal.<break time="1.5s"/> They will never rot away<break time="600ms"/> forgotten in the mountain's belly.<break time="1.5s"/> I have saved them."
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<!-- The Raid -->
<prosody rate="medium-slow" pitch="-1st">
Marshal Price knew<break time="600ms"/> he couldn't wait any longer.<break time="1.5s"/> He assembled every able-bodied man in town<break time="800ms"/> twelve in total<break time="800ms"/> and prepared to enter the mines.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="medium">
Word had spread through the community<break time="500ms"/> about Cooper's discovery,<break time="800ms"/> and the mood was volatile.<break time="1s"/> Price had to physically restrain several men<break time="600ms"/> who wanted to burn down Constance's house immediately,<break time="800ms"/> damn the evidence<break time="500ms"/> and damn the law.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="medium" pitch="-1st">
But Constance Blackwood<break time="1s"/> was not a woman<break time="600ms"/> who could be taken<break time="500ms"/> by surprise.
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
When Price and his men arrived at her house<break time="600ms"/> on a misty September morning,<break time="1s"/> they found it<break time="800ms"/> empty.<break time="1.5s"/> The door was unlocked,<break time="800ms"/> swinging gently in the mountain wind<break time="600ms"/> that seemed to carry voices from the peaks above<break time="1s"/> or perhaps<break time="600ms"/> that was just imagination.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="medium-slow">
Inside,<break time="600ms"/> the rooms were bare<break time="600ms"/> except for a single table<break time="500ms"/> in the center of the main room.<break time="1s"/> The house had been stripped<break time="500ms"/> of most personal belongings,<break time="800ms"/> as if she'd been preparing to leave<break time="500ms"/> for some time.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
On that table was a map<break time="600ms"/> of the mine system,<break time="800ms"/> drawn in meticulous detail<break time="600ms"/> that demonstrated an intimate knowledge<break time="500ms"/> of the underground tunnels.<break time="1s"/> The map was far more accurate<break time="500ms"/> than the official mining company surveys,<break time="800ms"/> showing passages and chambers<break time="500ms"/> that didn't appear<break time="400ms"/> on any recorded plans.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
A route was marked in red ink,<break time="800ms"/> leading from the nearest mine entrance<break time="600ms"/> to her workshop<break time="600ms"/> deep beneath the mountain.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" pitch="-1st">
It was an invitation.<break time="1.5s"/> Or perhaps<break time="1s"/> a challenge.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
Beside the map was a note,<break time="800ms"/> written in the same elegant handwriting<break time="500ms"/> that filled her journal:
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft" pitch="-2st">
"Come and see<break time="600ms"/> what I have created.<break time="1.5s"/> Come and understand<break time="600ms"/> what art truly means.<break time="1.5s"/> The gallery awaits<break time="800ms"/> its final visitors."
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<!-- Entering the Gallery -->
<prosody rate="slow">
The men followed the marked route<break time="600ms"/> through the darkness,<break time="800ms"/> their lanterns casting wild shadows<break time="500ms"/> on the tunnel walls.<break time="1s"/> Water dripped from above,<break time="600ms"/> each drop echoing through the passages<break time="500ms"/> like a ticking clock.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
The air grew colder as they descended,<break time="800ms"/> thick with the smell of lime<break time="600ms"/> and something else<break time="1s"/> something sweet and rotten<break time="800ms"/> that made their stomachs turn<break time="600ms"/> and their throats close.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
The timbers that supported the tunnels<break time="500ms"/> were old and rotting,<break time="800ms"/> creaking ominously with every step they took,<break time="800ms"/> occasionally shedding showers of dirt<break time="500ms"/> and small stones<break time="500ms"/> that pattered onto their hats.
</prosody>

<break time="2.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" pitch="-1st">
They found the workshop<break time="800ms"/> exactly as Cooper had described it.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
The skeletal tableaus lined the walls<break time="600ms"/> of a vast natural chamber,<break time="800ms"/> easily fifty feet across<break time="500ms"/> and thirty feet high,<break time="800ms"/> its ceiling lost in darkness<break time="600ms"/> above the reach of their lanterns.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
The chamber was lit<break time="600ms"/> by dozens<break time="800ms"/> perhaps hundreds<break time="800ms"/> of candles<break time="800ms"/> that Constance must have placed there<break time="500ms"/> in anticipation of their arrival.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" pitch="-1st">
The effect was nightmarish<break time="1s"/> shadows dancing across the posed skeletons,<break time="800ms"/> making them seem almost alive<break time="600ms"/> in the flickering light,<break time="1s"/> as if they were breathing,<break time="600ms"/> moving,<break time="600ms"/> watching the intruders<break time="600ms"/> with empty eye sockets<break time="800ms"/> that somehow seemed<break time="800ms"/> accusatory.
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
But Constance herself<break time="1s"/> was nowhere to be found.
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<!-- Sarah Mitchell's Remains -->
<prosody rate="medium-slow">
What they did find<break time="800ms"/> was her final creation,<break time="800ms"/> still incomplete on her main workbench.<break time="1s"/> The skeleton was freshly cleaned,<break time="600ms"/> the bones still showing traces<break time="500ms"/> of the chemicals she'd used,<break time="800ms"/> still retaining a slight yellow tinge<break time="600ms"/> that would fade to pure white<break time="500ms"/> with time and exposure.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" pitch="-2st">
Next to it lay identification papers<break time="800ms"/> that made Marshal Price's blood<break time="600ms"/> run cold.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="medium">
The skeleton<break time="1s"/> was James Cooper's fiancée,<break time="1.5s"/> Sarah Mitchell.
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
The recognition hit Cooper<break time="600ms"/> like a physical blow.<break time="1s"/> He fell to his knees<break time="600ms"/> beside the workbench,<break time="800ms"/> reaching out to touch the bones<break time="1s"/> all that remained<break time="600ms"/> of the woman he'd loved,<break time="800ms"/> the woman he'd planned to marry,<break time="800ms"/> the woman who'd been reduced to components<break time="600ms"/> for someone else's twisted art.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" pitch="-1st">
He made a sound<break time="800ms"/> that was barely human,<break time="1s"/> a keening wail<break time="800ms"/> that echoed through the chamber<break time="800ms"/> and seemed to be answered<break time="600ms"/> by the whisper of wind<break time="500ms"/> through the tunnels.
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<prosody rate="medium-slow">
And arranged around the workshop<break time="600ms"/> were the personal effects of all forty-three victims,<break time="800ms"/> carefully catalogued and preserved<break time="500ms"/> in wooden boxes<break time="500ms"/> lined with velvet.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
Wedding rings.<break time="800ms"/> Photographs in tarnished frames.<break time="800ms"/> Letters from loved ones,<break time="500ms"/> their ink fading.<break time="1s"/> A child's toy carved from wood.<break time="1s"/> A miner's pocket watch,<break time="600ms"/> still ticking somehow.<break time="1s"/> A woman's locket<break time="500ms"/> containing a faded daguerreotype.<break time="1s"/> A Bible with a family tree<break time="500ms"/> inscribed on the front page.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
Constance had kept everything,<break time="800ms"/> creating not just a gallery of death<break time="800ms"/> but a museum<break time="800ms"/> of stolen lives.
</prosody>

<break time="2.5s"/>

<prosody rate="medium">
Each box was labeled<break time="500ms"/> with a name,<break time="500ms"/> a date,<break time="500ms"/> and a brief description<break time="500ms"/> written in Constance's elegant handwriting.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
"William Tate<break time="800ms"/> March fifteenth, eighteen eighty-seven<break time="1s"/> A wanderer who sought fortune in the earth.<break time="1s"/> His bones now stand eternal guard<break time="600ms"/> at my gallery's entrance,<break time="800ms"/> forever watching<break time="500ms"/> for what he never found in life."
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
"Sarah Mitchell<break time="800ms"/> April second, eighteen eighty-seven<break time="1s"/> Young and beautiful,<break time="800ms"/> she brings grace to my ballroom scene,<break time="800ms"/> dancing forever<break time="600ms"/> in the candlelight."
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<!-- The Memorial Discovery -->
<prosody rate="medium-slow">
One particularly disturbing tableau<break time="600ms"/> depicted a mining scene.<break time="1s"/> Five skeletons were positioned<break time="500ms"/> as if working in a tunnel,<break time="800ms"/> their bones posed in the act<break time="500ms"/> of swinging pickaxes<break time="500ms"/> and pushing coal carts.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
The tools were real,<break time="600ms"/> scavenged from abandoned equipment.<break time="1s"/> At the center of the scene<break time="600ms"/> was a single skeleton<break time="500ms"/> lying on the ground,<break time="800ms"/> partially buried under a pile<break time="500ms"/> of real coal and broken timber.<break time="1s"/> Other skeletons were positioned<break time="500ms"/> as if reaching toward the buried figure,<break time="800ms"/> trying to dig it out.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
A small brass plaque beside the display<break time="600ms"/> was engraved with text:
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" pitch="-1st">
"In Memory of My Beloved Husband,<break time="800ms"/> Marcus Blackwood,<break time="800ms"/> and the Seventeen Men Who Died With Him<break time="600ms"/> on March twelfth, eighteen eighty-two<break time="1.5s"/> May Their Bones Rest<break time="600ms"/> Where Their Lives Were Taken."
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
It was then that Marshal Price understood<break time="800ms"/> the full scope<break time="600ms"/> of Constance's madness.<break time="1.5s"/> This wasn't just about killing.<break time="1s"/> It wasn't even about preserving bones<break time="600ms"/> or creating art.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" pitch="-1st">
It was about creating a permanent memorial<break time="800ms"/> to the mining disaster<break time="600ms"/> that had taken her husband's life.<break time="1.5s"/> Every skeleton in her collection<break time="600ms"/> represented not just a victim,<break time="800ms"/> but a player<break time="600ms"/> in an elaborate theatrical representation<break time="600ms"/> of grief,<break time="600ms"/> loss,<break time="800ms"/> and the crushing weight<break time="600ms"/> of Appalachian isolation.
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
Price realized with growing horror<break time="800ms"/> that Constance had been recreating her world.<break time="1.5s"/> The skeletons weren't random.<break time="1s"/> Each represented a specific type of person<break time="500ms"/> from the community.<break time="1s"/> There were miners and merchants,<break time="600ms"/> women and children,<break time="600ms"/> the young and the old.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
She was building a town of the dead<break time="800ms"/> beneath the mountain,<break time="1s"/> a permanent population<break time="600ms"/> that would never leave,<break time="600ms"/> never abandon her,<break time="800ms"/> never die<break time="600ms"/> and leave her alone<break time="800ms"/> again.
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<!-- The Search -->
<prosody rate="medium-slow" pitch="-1st">
The search for Constance Blackwood<break time="800ms"/> consumed the next three months.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="medium">
Posses scoured the mountains<break time="500ms"/> and the hollows beyond Widow's Hollow.<break time="1s"/> Telegraph wires carried her description<break time="500ms"/> to every town<break time="400ms"/> in West Virginia,<break time="400ms"/> Kentucky,<break time="400ms"/> and Tennessee.<break time="1s"/> Wanted posters appeared in post offices<break time="500ms"/> throughout the region,<break time="800ms"/> describing her as extremely dangerous<break time="500ms"/> and likely insane.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
The reward for her capture<break time="600ms"/> climbed to five hundred dollars<break time="1s"/> a fortune<break time="600ms"/> in a region where most men<break time="500ms"/> earned less than a dollar a day.
</prosody>

<break time="2.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft" pitch="-1st">
But the Bone Collector<break time="1s"/> had vanished<break time="600ms"/> into the vast Appalachian wilderness<break time="800ms"/> as completely as morning fog<break time="600ms"/> burns off in sunlight.
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
Some believed she'd died in the mountains,<break time="800ms"/> perhaps falling into one of the countless abandoned mine shafts<break time="600ms"/> that dotted the region<break time="500ms"/> like open graves.<break time="1s"/> The mountains were full of ways to die<break time="800ms"/> starvation,<break time="500ms"/> exposure,<break time="500ms"/> wild animals,<break time="500ms"/> accidents.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
Others thought she'd fled west,<break time="600ms"/> changing her name<break time="500ms"/> and starting over<break time="500ms"/> in some distant territory<break time="500ms"/> where no one would recognize her,<break time="1s"/> perhaps continuing her work<break time="600ms"/> in new, undiscovered galleries<break time="600ms"/> beneath different mountains.
</prosody>

<break time="2.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
There were even those<break time="600ms"/> who claimed to have seen her<break time="600ms"/> in other mining towns,<break time="1s"/> always watching from a distance,<break time="800ms"/> always dressed in black,<break time="800ms"/> always alone,<break time="800ms"/> always lingering<break time="600ms"/> near the entrances to abandoned mines.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
But none of these sightings<break time="600ms"/> were ever confirmed,<break time="800ms"/> and pursuit always ended<break time="600ms"/> in dead ends<break time="600ms"/> and frustration.
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<!-- The Aftermath -->
<prosody rate="medium-slow">
The discovery in the mine<break time="600ms"/> attracted attention<break time="500ms"/> from far beyond the Appalachian region.<break time="1s"/> Newspapers in New York,<break time="500ms"/> Philadelphia,<break time="500ms"/> and Boston<break time="600ms"/> published sensationalist accounts<break time="500ms"/> of the "Appalachian Bone Witch."
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="medium">
Medical examiners and criminologists<break time="500ms"/> traveled to Widow's Hollow<break time="500ms"/> to study Constance's work.<break time="1s"/> Some were horrified by what they found.<break time="1s"/> Others were grudgingly impressed<break time="600ms"/> by the technical skill demonstrated<break time="500ms"/> in her articulations.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
The debate over whether her work<break time="500ms"/> should be preserved for scientific study<break time="600ms"/> or destroyed as evidence<break time="500ms"/> of unspeakable evil<break time="800ms"/> raged for weeks.
</prosody>

<break time="2.5s"/>

<prosody rate="medium-slow">
Meanwhile,<break time="600ms"/> the town of Widow's Hollow<break time="600ms"/> began to die<break time="600ms"/> more quickly<break time="500ms"/> than even the failing coal mines<break time="500ms"/> could have killed it.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
The discovery of the bone gallery<break time="600ms"/> drove away the few remaining families.<break time="1s"/> No one wanted to live in a place<break time="500ms"/> where such horror had flourished undetected<break time="500ms"/> for years,<break time="800ms"/> where neighbors had walked past a monster<break time="600ms"/> without seeing her true nature,<break time="800ms"/> where the mountain had proven itself hungry<break time="600ms"/> not just for coal miners<break time="800ms"/> but for everyone foolish enough<break time="500ms"/> to remain in its shadow.
</prosody>

<break time="2.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
By eighteen ninety,<break time="800ms"/> just three years after Constance's disappearance,<break time="1s"/> the town was completely deserted,<break time="800ms"/> left to be reclaimed<break time="500ms"/> by the mountains.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
Houses stood empty,<break time="600ms"/> their windows dark and vacant.<break time="1s"/> The church where Reverend Blackburn had once preached<break time="600ms"/> fell into ruin.<break time="1s"/> The general store was looted by passing travelers,<break time="800ms"/> then left to rot.
</prosody>

<break time="2.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" pitch="-1st">
The mine entrance<break time="600ms"/> where Constance had created her gallery<break time="800ms"/> was sealed by order of the state,<break time="1s"/> tons of rock and timber<break time="500ms"/> used to block access.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
But that didn't stop curiosity seekers<break time="600ms"/> from breaking in.<break time="1s"/> For decades,<break time="600ms"/> people would enter those tunnels<break time="500ms"/> seeking souvenirs<break time="600ms"/> or simply wanting to see the place<break time="500ms"/> where such madness had taken root.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
Most found nothing<break time="1s"/> the authorities had removed all of Constance's displays<break time="600ms"/> and burned them in a massive bonfire<break time="600ms"/> that reportedly smoldered for three days,<break time="1s"/> filling the hollow with acrid smoke<break time="600ms"/> that smelled of lime<break time="800ms"/> and something worse.
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<!-- The Kentucky Cabin -->
<prosody rate="medium-slow" pitch="-1st">
In nineteen oh-three,<break time="800ms"/> sixteen years after Constance's disappearance,<break time="1s"/> a hunter in the mountains of eastern Kentucky<break time="600ms"/> discovered a small cabin<break time="600ms"/> hidden in a remote hollow<break time="600ms"/> accessible only by a treacherous trail<break time="600ms"/> that wound through terrain so difficult<break time="600ms"/> that most people would consider it<break time="500ms"/> impassable.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
The cabin was well-constructed,<break time="600ms"/> built by someone with knowledge<break time="500ms"/> of mountain survival,<break time="800ms"/> and it showed signs of having been occupied<break time="600ms"/> recently.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="medium-slow">
Inside,<break time="600ms"/> he found evidence that a woman had been living there<break time="800ms"/> a woman living alone,<break time="600ms"/> judging by the clothes and personal items.<break time="1s"/> The cabin was sparse but functional,<break time="600ms"/> with a bed,<break time="400ms"/> a table,<break time="400ms"/> shelves of preserved food,<break time="600ms"/> and tools for surviving in the wilderness.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" pitch="-1st">
But what caught the hunter's attention<break time="800ms"/> was the workshop<break time="800ms"/> in the back room.
</prosody>

<break time="2.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
There were tools for cleaning bones<break time="800ms"/> knives,<break time="500ms"/> scrapers,<break time="500ms"/> containers of chemicals<break time="500ms"/> whose labels had been carefully removed.<break time="1s"/> There were bottles of preservatives<break time="500ms"/> and bleaching agents.<break time="1.5s"/> And on a workbench,<break time="800ms"/> illuminated by light streaming through a single window,<break time="1s"/> was a human skeleton<break time="600ms"/> articulated on a custom stand,<break time="800ms"/> positioned as if reading a book.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
The book was real,<break time="800ms"/> lying open in the skeleton's bony grasp,<break time="1s"/> its pages yellowed with age.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
On the wall was a journal entry,<break time="800ms"/> written in elegant handwriting<break time="500ms"/> on a piece of paper<break time="500ms"/> tacked to the logs:
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft" pitch="-2st">
"Time has not diminished my vision.<break time="1s"/> The mountains continue to provide.<break time="1.5s"/> My gallery continues to grow,<break time="800ms"/> though now I am more careful,<break time="600ms"/> more selective.<break time="1s"/> I have learned from past mistakes.<break time="1.5s"/> The work continues,<break time="800ms"/> always the work,<break time="800ms"/> until I too<break time="600ms"/> become part of it."
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<prosody rate="medium-slow">
By the time authorities reached the cabin,<break time="600ms"/> following the hunter's directions<break time="500ms"/> through terrain that took two days to traverse,<break time="1s"/> it was empty.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
But the discovery sparked renewed interest<break time="600ms"/> in the Bone Collector case.<break time="1s"/> Had Constance Blackwood been alive all this time,<break time="800ms"/> continuing her work<break time="500ms"/> in even more remote locations?<break time="1s"/> Were there other galleries<break time="500ms"/> hidden in the vast expanse<break time="500ms"/> of Appalachian wilderness,<break time="800ms"/> undiscovered monuments<break time="600ms"/> to her particular brand of madness?
</prosody>

<break time="2.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
The question was never answered.
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<!-- The Fates of Others -->
<prosody rate="medium-slow">
James Cooper,<break time="600ms"/> the man who discovered her gallery,<break time="800ms"/> never recovered from what he saw<break time="500ms"/> in those mines.<break time="1s"/> He left Widow's Hollow immediately<break time="500ms"/> after giving his testimony,<break time="800ms"/> his belongings packed in less than an hour,<break time="800ms"/> his goodbyes said to no one.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
He disappeared into anonymity,<break time="600ms"/> changing his name<break time="500ms"/> and trying to build a new life<break time="500ms"/> far from the mountains<break time="500ms"/> that had taken everything from him.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
Some say he became a wandering preacher,<break time="800ms"/> traveling through isolated communities<break time="600ms"/> and warning them about the evil<break time="500ms"/> that can grow in places<break time="500ms"/> where people live too far<break time="500ms"/> from civilization's light.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
Others claim he went mad,<break time="800ms"/> spending his final years in an asylum in Pennsylvania,<break time="1s"/> drawing skeletal figures<break time="500ms"/> over and over<break time="500ms"/> on any surface he could find<break time="800ms"/> walls,<break time="500ms"/> floors,<break time="600ms"/> his own arms.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
The staff reportedly found his cell<break time="600ms"/> covered in bone drawings after his death<break time="600ms"/> in nineteen twelve,<break time="1s"/> each skeleton posed in elaborate tableaus<break time="600ms"/> that echoed what he'd seen<break time="500ms"/> in Constance's gallery<break time="600ms"/> a quarter century earlier.
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<prosody rate="medium-slow">
Marshal Dalton Price<break time="600ms"/> spent the rest of his career<break time="500ms"/> haunted by the case.<break time="1s"/> He kept a file on Constance Blackwood<break time="500ms"/> in a locked drawer in his office,<break time="800ms"/> adding any reports of similar crimes<break time="500ms"/> or sightings of a woman<break time="400ms"/> matching her description.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
By the time he retired in nineteen ten,<break time="800ms"/> the file had grown to hundreds of pages,<break time="1s"/> documenting dozens of unsolved disappearances<break time="600ms"/> in mining towns throughout Appalachia.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
Price became convinced<break time="600ms"/> that Constance had never stopped,<break time="1s"/> that somewhere in the mountains,<break time="800ms"/> she was still collecting,<break time="600ms"/> still creating,<break time="800ms"/> still building her gallery of bones.
</prosody>

<break time="2.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" pitch="-1st">
On his deathbed in nineteen fifteen,<break time="800ms"/> Price called his successor to his side<break time="600ms"/> and gave him the file.
</prosody>

<break time="1.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
"She's still out there,"<break time="1s"/> he whispered,<break time="600ms"/> his voice weak but insistent.<break time="1.5s"/> "I know it.<break time="800ms"/> I can feel it.<break time="1s"/> Somewhere in these mountains,<break time="800ms"/> she's still working.<break time="1.5s"/> Promise me<break time="800ms"/> you'll keep looking."
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<!-- The 1982 Discovery -->
<prosody rate="medium-slow" pitch="-1st">
In nineteen eighty-two,<break time="800ms"/> exactly one hundred years<break time="600ms"/> after the tunnel collapse<break time="500ms"/> that killed Marcus Blackwood,<break time="1s"/> a bizarre discovery was made<break time="600ms"/> in a cave in southwestern Virginia.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="medium">
Hikers found a sealed chamber<break time="600ms"/> containing a single skeleton,<break time="800ms"/> carefully articulated and posed<break time="500ms"/> in a sitting position.<break time="1s"/> The skeleton was positioned at a small table,<break time="600ms"/> with a pen held in its bony fingers<break time="600ms"/> and a journal lying open before it.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
The journal contained a single entry,<break time="800ms"/> written in elegant handwriting<break time="500ms"/> that matched samples<break time="400ms"/> from Constance's original journal:
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft" pitch="-2st">
"I have completed my final work.<break time="1s"/> Forty-three souls preserved,<break time="800ms"/> each one a masterpiece,<break time="800ms"/> each one eternal.<break time="1.5s"/> But I have saved the finest subject<break time="600ms"/> for last<break time="1s"/> myself.<break time="1.5s"/> Let whoever finds this know<break time="600ms"/> that I chose when and how<break time="500ms"/> my story would end.<break time="1.5s"/> Let them know that I am not a victim<break time="600ms"/> of time or decay,<break time="800ms"/> but a willing participant<break time="600ms"/> in the art I have created.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft" pitch="-2st">
My bones will be the forty-fourth<break time="800ms"/> and final piece<break time="600ms"/> in my gallery.<break time="1.5s"/> May they rest<break time="600ms"/> where my husband's bones rest,<break time="800ms"/> deep in the mountain's embrace."
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<prosody rate="medium-slow">
DNA testing on the skeleton was inconclusive<break time="800ms"/> the bones were old,<break time="600ms"/> consistent with death occurring decades earlier,<break time="800ms"/> but exact identification was impossible.<break time="1s"/> The handwriting matched,<break time="600ms"/> but handwriting could be forged.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
Some believed it was genuinely Constance,<break time="800ms"/> that she'd spent her final years<break time="600ms"/> preparing her own skeleton for display,<break time="800ms"/> then sealed herself in that cave<break time="500ms"/> to die.<break time="1s"/> Others thought it was an elaborate hoax,<break time="800ms"/> someone's twisted tribute<break time="500ms"/> to the legend.
</prosody>

<break time="2.5s"/>

<prosody rate="medium">
The skeleton was eventually turned over<break time="500ms"/> to the Smithsonian Institution,<break time="800ms"/> where it remains in their collection<break time="500ms"/> to this day,<break time="800ms"/> catalogued simply as<break time="600ms"/> "Female,<break time="500ms"/> approximately forty to fifty years old,<break time="600ms"/> late nineteenth century,<break time="800ms"/> circumstances of death unknown."
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
Sometimes,<break time="600ms"/> staff members report<break time="500ms"/> that the skeleton's position<break time="500ms"/> seems to change slightly<break time="500ms"/> between viewings,<break time="1s"/> though this is always attributed<break time="500ms"/> to tricks of light<break time="600ms"/> or memory.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" pitch="-1st">
But there are those who swear<break time="600ms"/> that the skull's empty eye sockets<break time="600ms"/> seem to watch them,<break time="1s"/> that the bony fingers holding the pen<break time="600ms"/> appear poised to write more,<break time="1s"/> that there's an air of satisfaction<break time="600ms"/> emanating from the display,<break time="1s"/> as if the subject is pleased<break time="800ms"/> with how the story ended.
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<!-- Modern Day -->
<prosody rate="medium-slow">
Today,<break time="600ms"/> more than a century later,<break time="800ms"/> the story of Constance Blackwood<break time="500ms"/> remains one of the most disturbing cases<break time="500ms"/> in Appalachian history.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
The site of Widow's Hollow is long gone,<break time="800ms"/> reclaimed by forest and fog,<break time="800ms"/> with only a few crumbling foundations<break time="500ms"/> marking where the town once stood.<break time="1s"/> The sealed mine entrance has collapsed completely,<break time="800ms"/> burying whatever evidence might have remained.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
But the story persists,<break time="800ms"/> passed down through generations,<break time="800ms"/> each telling adding new details<break time="500ms"/> or removing old ones<break time="600ms"/> until the line between history and legend<break time="600ms"/> blurs beyond recognition.
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" pitch="-1st">
On foggy nights in the mountains of West Virginia,<break time="1s"/> locals still tell stories<break time="600ms"/> about the Bone Collector.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
They warn hikers<break time="500ms"/> not to venture into abandoned mines,<break time="800ms"/> not just because of physical dangers,<break time="800ms"/> but because some say<break time="600ms"/> that Constance's spirit<break time="500ms"/> still walks those tunnels,<break time="1s"/> still searching for subjects<break time="500ms"/> for her eternal gallery.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
They speak of hearing sounds deep underground<break time="1s"/> the scrape of bone on stone,<break time="1s"/> the whisper of someone working<break time="500ms"/> with inhuman patience<break time="500ms"/> in the darkness,<break time="1s"/> the faint echo of humming<break time="600ms"/> as unseen hands<break time="500ms"/> arrange and rearrange displays<break time="600ms"/> that no living person<break time="500ms"/> will ever see.
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
And sometimes,<break time="600ms"/> in the most remote hollows of Appalachia,<break time="1s"/> hunters and hikers report<break time="500ms"/> finding strange things.<break time="1.5s"/> Bones arranged in patterns<break time="500ms"/> that couldn't be natural<break time="1s"/> a circle of deer skulls,<break time="800ms"/> a tower of carefully stacked vertebrae,<break time="800ms"/> small skeletons posed<break time="500ms"/> as if dancing<break time="500ms"/> or playing<break time="600ms"/> or simply standing watch.
</prosody>

<break time="2.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
Are these the remnants<break time="600ms"/> of Constance's original work,<break time="800ms"/> missed by the authorities<break time="500ms"/> who cleared out her gallery?<break time="1.5s"/> Are they the work of copycat killers<break time="600ms"/> inspired by her legend?<break time="1.5s"/> Or is it possible<break time="800ms"/> that somewhere in the vast Appalachian wilderness,<break time="1s"/> in some hollow so remote<break time="500ms"/> that it appears on no map,<break time="1s"/> the Bone Collector<break time="600ms"/> continues her work<break time="500ms"/> even now,<break time="1s"/> adding to a gallery<break time="600ms"/> that may never be discovered?
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" pitch="-2st">
The question hangs in the mountain air<break time="800ms"/> like morning mist,<break time="1s"/> unanswered<break time="800ms"/> and unanswerable.
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<!-- Final Reflection -->
<prosody rate="medium-slow">
What we know for certain is this:<break time="1s"/> Constance Blackwood transformed grief<break time="600ms"/> into something monstrous.<break time="1s"/> She turned loss into art,<break time="600ms"/> death into display,<break time="800ms"/> and human beings into objects<break time="500ms"/> to be collected and arranged<break time="500ms"/> according to her twisted vision.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow">
She showed that isolation can corrupt<break time="600ms"/> even the most civilized soul,<break time="1s"/> that the darkness in the human heart<break time="600ms"/> can find expression in ways<break time="500ms"/> that defy comprehension.<break time="1.5s"/> She proved that monsters<break time="600ms"/> don't always announce themselves<break time="500ms"/> with violence and rage<break time="1s"/> sometimes they move quietly through the world,<break time="800ms"/> seemingly ordinary,<break time="800ms"/> until the day their work<break time="600ms"/> is finally revealed.
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
The mountains of Appalachia<break time="800ms"/> have always kept secrets.<break time="1.5s"/> They've hidden moonshine stills and fugitives,<break time="800ms"/> buried treasure and terrible crimes.<break time="1s"/> They've swallowed people whole,<break time="800ms"/> leaving families to wonder forever<break time="600ms"/> what happened to their loved ones.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" pitch="-1st">
But few secrets are as dark<break time="800ms"/> as the one that grew<break time="600ms"/> in the abandoned mines of Widow's Hollow,<break time="1s"/> where a grieving widow became something<break time="600ms"/> far worse than a simple killer.
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
She became an artist of death.<break time="1s"/> A curator of bones.<break time="1.5s"/> A woman who looked at human remains<break time="600ms"/> and saw not horror,<break time="800ms"/> but beauty.<break time="1.5s"/> Not victims,<break time="800ms"/> but masterpieces.<break time="1.5s"/> Not an end,<break time="800ms"/> but a transformation into something<break time="600ms"/> she believed was eternal.
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" pitch="-2st">
And somewhere in those mountains,<break time="1s"/> in the deep places<break time="600ms"/> where sunlight never reaches<break time="600ms"/> and human voices never echo,<break time="1.5s"/> some believe her gallery<break time="800ms"/> still stands.<break time="1.5s"/> Waiting.<break time="1s"/> Growing.<break time="1.5s"/> Maintained by hands<break time="600ms"/> that should have turned to dust<break time="500ms"/> decades ago,<break time="1s"/> or perhaps by new hands<break time="600ms"/> inspired by her vision,<break time="800ms"/> continuing the work she started.
</prosody>

<break time="4s"/>

<!-- Final Warning -->
<prosody rate="slow" volume="medium" pitch="-1st">
The Bone Collector of Widow's Hollow.<break time="1.5s"/> Remember her name.<break time="1.5s"/> Remember her story.
</prosody>

<break time="2.5s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
And if you ever find yourself<break time="600ms"/> in the abandoned mines of Appalachia,<break time="1s"/> in tunnels that smell of lime<break time="600ms"/> and old death,<break time="1.5s"/> and you hear the sound of someone working<break time="600ms"/> in the darkness ahead<break time="1.5s"/> the clink of tools on bone,<break time="1s"/> the whisper of wire being threaded,<break time="1s"/> the satisfied hum of an artist<break time="600ms"/> absorbed in her work<break time="2s"/>
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="loud" pitch="-2st">
Turn back.
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
Some galleries<break time="800ms"/> were never meant to be viewed<break time="600ms"/> by the living.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
Some art<break time="800ms"/> was never meant to be appreciated<break time="600ms"/> by sane minds.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft" pitch="-1st">
And some stories<break time="1s"/> are best left buried<break time="800ms"/> in the darkness<break time="800ms"/> where they belong.
</prosody>

<break time="5s"/>

<!-- Outro -->
<prosody rate="medium">
So what did you think<break time="500ms"/> of this journey into one of Appalachia's darkest chapters?<break time="1s"/> The story of Constance Blackwood<break time="500ms"/> reminds us that true horror<break time="500ms"/> doesn't always announce itself<break time="400ms"/> with screams and violence.<break time="1s"/> Sometimes it grows slowly,<break time="600ms"/> in isolation,<break time="800ms"/> transforming grief<break time="500ms"/> into something unspeakable.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="medium">
If you enjoyed this descent<break time="400ms"/> into the darkness beneath the mountains,<break time="800ms"/> don't forget to leave your like<break time="500ms"/> and subscribe to Unwanted Visitors<break time="600ms"/> for more stories from the shadows<break time="400ms"/> of American history.<break time="1s"/> The mountains have many secrets,<break time="600ms"/> and we're just beginning to uncover them.
</prosody>

<break time="2s"/>

<prosody rate="slow" volume="soft">
Until next time,<break time="800ms"/> stay safe out there.<break time="1.5s"/> And remember:<break time="1s"/> the mountains keep their secrets well.<break time="1.5s"/> Perhaps<break time="1s"/> too well.
</prosody>

<break time="3s"/>

</speak>